♪The painting is filled with old dreams and the moonlight is scattered♪
♪ اللوحة مليئة بالأحلام القديمة وضوء القمر متناثر ♪
♪I draw a flower when the light is half dim♪
♪ أرسم زهرة عندما يكون الضوء نصف خافت
♪The wind blows through the eyebrows and the insanity remains♪
تهب الرياح عبر الحاجبين ويبقى الجنون ♪
♪One more step and everything will be fine♪
♪ خطوة أخرى وسيكون كل شيء على ما يرام
♪Who says that things are unpredictable? You're still around♪
♪ من قال أن الأشياء لا يمكن التنبؤ بها؟  أنت ما زلت في الجوار ♪
♪The lonely shadows of the past have gone♪
اختفت الظلال الوحيدة للماضي
♪I'll take the hardships and turn them into liquor♪
♪ سآخذ المصاعب وأحولها إلى خمور
♪Old friends will never be forgotten♪
♪ لن يُنسى الأصدقاء القدامى
♪Who says the world has changed? You never left♪
♪ من قال أن العالم قد تغير؟  أنت لم تغادر أبدًا ♪
♪Yesterday's sorrows and joys are long gone♪
ولت منذ فترة طويلة أحزان وأفراح الأمس ♪
♪I hold the light in my hands only to see this love last♪
♪ أحمل الضوء في يدي فقط لأرى هذا الحب أخيرًا
♪A million dreams for me to look back on♪
♪ مليون حلم بالنسبة لي لأنظر إليها مرة أخرى ♪
=Order of the Sommelier= =Episode 3=
= ترتيب الساقي = = الحلقة 3 =
(Underage viewers are advised to watch under parental consent.)
(يُنصح المشاهدين القاصرين بالمشاهدة بموافقة الوالدين).
I've been on the run all day.
لقد كنت هاربًا طوال اليوم.
I'm starving.
أنا جائع.
I wonder if there are
أتساءل ما إذا كان هناك
grouse in the woods.
احتج في الغابة.
You should have told me earlier.
كان يجب أن تخبرني في وقت سابق.
Wait.
انتظر.
Here. Eat this.
هنا.  كل هذا.
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Wheat bread.
خبز حنطة.
I made it.
لقد فعلتها.
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
Try it.
جربها.
(Why do humans like to eat)
(لماذا يحب البشر تناول الطعام)
(food made from grass?)
(طعام مصنوع من العشب؟)
(I won't eat it.)
(لن آكله.)
(I want to eat meat.)
(أريد أن آكل اللحوم).
Yummy!
لذيذ!
(Hu Shen)
(هو شين)
My name is Hu Shen.
اسمي هو شين.
From now on, we are friends.
من الآن فصاعدا ، نحن أصدقاء.
This is unexpected.
هذا غير متوقع.
I had no friends
ليس لدي أصدقاء
in my village,
في قريتي،
but I became friends with
لكني أصبحت صديقًا له
someone from Hedong Village.
شخص من قرية Hedong.
This is new to me, too.
هذا جديد بالنسبة لي أيضا.
I can't believe a human...
لا أصدق إنسان ...
I can't believe I'm making friends with
لا أصدق أنني أقوم بتكوين صداقات مع
someone from Hexi Village.
شخص من قرية هيكسي.
It's going to rain.
ستمطر.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
Tomorrow you come here
غدا أتيت إلى هنا
and I'll bring you more wheat breads.
وسأحضر لك المزيد من خبز القمح.
All right.
حسنًا.
See you tomorrow.
أراك غدا.
(Hedong Village) Where did the fox go?
(قرية هيدونغ) أين ذهب الثعلب؟
Little Loach.
(قرية هيدونج)
I want to drink.
اريد ان اشرب.
Give me the liquor.
أعطني الخمور.
Do you know how long it takes
هل تعرف كم من الوقت يستغرق
to brew Sober Demon?
لتخمير شيطان رصين؟
At the rate you're drinking,
بالمعدل الذي تشربه ،
my tavern will be bankrupt
سوف تفلس خارتي
before you can catch
قبل أن تتمكن من اللحاق
a single demon.
شيطان واحد.
You brought it to me.
أحضرته لي.
Fine.
بخير.
I was befuddled.
كنت في حيرة من أمري.
I don't have any liquor with me.
ليس لدي أي خمور معي.
I'll take you back to the tavern, okay?
سأعيدك إلى الحانة ، حسنًا؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
(Demon Tavern)
(حانة شيطان)
Listen.
يستمع.
The guy Master Bai Qi
الرجل سيد باي تشي
brought in
جلبت
looked so much like the demon hunter.
يشبه إلى حد كبير صائد الشياطين.
I was freaking out.
أنا كان ينقط خارجا.
I won't say look alike.
لن أقول انظروا على حد سواء.
He is
هو
exactly identical.
متطابق تماما.
Master Bai Qi.
سيد باي تشي.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
I mean,
أعني،
run for your life!
انج بحياتك!
Run!
يجري!
Run! Quick!
يجري!  سريع!
(Demon Tavern) Run!
(حانة الشيطان) اركض!
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
I never thought
لم أظن طلاقا
you could make such good liquor.
يمكنك صنع الخمور الجيدة.
For the sake of this drink,
من أجل هذا المشروب ،
even if you were a bad loach,
حتى لو كنت لوش سيئًا ،
I wouldn't kill you.
لن أقتلك.
Admit it.
أعترف بذلك.
You also know that there are good and evil demons.
أنت تعلم أيضًا أن هناك شياطين صالحة وأشرار.
Why did you kill demons on sight before?
لماذا قتلت الشياطين في مرمى البصر من قبل؟
Yu, let's practise.
يو ، دعنا نتدرب.
No.
لا.
I don't want.
أنا لا أريد.
I'm afraid of heights.
أنا أخاف المرتفعات.
(Fu Yu's mother, Hu Die) Yu, it's all right.
(والدة فو يو ، هو داي) يو ، كل شيء على ما يرام.
- I am here. - No!
- أنا هنا.  - لا!
(Young Fu Yu) I'm afraid of heights.
(يونغ فو يو) أخاف من المرتفعات.
No.
(يونغ فو يو) لا.
(Young Fu Yu) Don't worry.
(يونغ فو يو) لا تقلق.
I will protect you.
سأحميك.
You demons
أيها الشياطين
put on a kind front
ضع في مقدمة طيبة
to achieve your goals.
لتحقيق أهدافك.
It's not genuine
إنه ليس أصليًا
(Demon Tavern)
(حانة الشيطان) إنها ليست حقيقية
because your hearts
(حانة شيطان) لأن قلوبكم
are made of iron and concrete.
(Demon Tavern) مصنوعة من الحديد والخرسانة.
(Demon Tavern)
(حانة شيطان)
There is no good, only evil.
(حانة الشيطان) ليس هناك خير ، شر فقط.
You...
أنت...
You, for example.
أنت على سبيل المثال.
You gave me liquor to drink
أعطيتني الخمور لأشربه
because you want my alchemy.
لأنك تريد الكيمياء الخاصة بي.
You told me the fox was a good demon
لقد أخبرتني أن الثعلب كان شيطانًا جيدًا
and not to kill it.
وليس قتله.
Your intention is to make me
نيتك هي أن تجعلني
think you're a good demon and spare you.
تعتقد أنك شيطان جيد وتجنيبك.
You are all the same.
كلكم نفس الشيء
Good and evil
خير و شر
are just tools
هي مجرد أدوات
to achieve your goals.
لتحقيق أهدافك.
Do you know
هل تعرف
why I agreed with you to
لماذا اتفقت معك على
a limit of 10,000 demons?
بحد 10000 شيطان؟
I love liquor,
انا احب الخمور
but I can't drink.
لكن لا يمكنني الشرب.
Liquor is like
مثل الخمور
a slow poison to me.
سم بطيء بالنسبة لي.
I did the math.
فعلت الرياضيات.
I'd probably only be able to
ربما سأكون قادرًا فقط على ذلك
kill 10,000 of them even if
قتل 10000 منهم حتى لو
I drank myself to death.
شربت نفسي حتى الموت.
You want to die
تريد الموت
and yet you killed so many innocent demons.
ومع ذلك فقد قتلت الكثير من الشياطين الأبرياء.
You yourself are ruthless,
أنت نفسك عديم الرحمة ،
yet you say that demons are all evil.
لكنك تقول ان كل الشياطين اشرار.
Fine.
بخير.
Then I'll raise the stakes.
ثم سأرفع المخاطر.
If that little fox harms anyone,
إذا كان هذا الثعلب الصغير يؤذي أي شخص ،
not only will I give up your alchemy,
لن أتخلى عن الكيمياء الخاصة بك فقط ،
I'll give my life
سأبذل حياتي
along with it.
جنبا إلى جنب معها.
You said it yourself.
قلت ذلك بنفسك.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
I've been holding back for a long time.
لقد كنت أتراجع لفترة طويلة.
It was
كان
a really torturous moment for me.
لحظة معذبة حقًا بالنسبة لي.
♪Which door to open so that I can see you again?♪
♪ أي باب يفتح حتى أتمكن من رؤيتك مرة أخرى؟
♪When the world is snowing heavily♪
♪ عندما يتساقط العالم بغزارة
♪I look back and you still look the same♪
♪ أنظر إلى الوراء وما زلت تبدو كما لو كنت
♪I lost my friends and started to wander♪
♪ فقدت أصدقائي وبدأت أتجول ♪
♪Which liquor shall I drink with you?♪
أي خمور أشرب معك؟
♪We'll drink and travel to a certain place♪
سنشرب ونسافر إلى مكان معين
♪The world and the spiritual realm are all connected♪
العالم والعالم الروحي مترابطان جميعًا ♪
♪Remembering the old days♪
تذكر الأيام الخوالي ♪
♪The past is quietly waiting to be unsealed♪
الماضي ينتظر بهدوء أن يُفتح ♪
♪It reminds me of my intent♪
يذكرني بنيتي ♪
♪Why is reality sometimes more like a dream than memories♪
♪ لماذا يكون الواقع أحيانًا أشبه بالحلم أكثر من الذكريات ♪
♪We promised to walk together through the glory♪
وعدنا أن نسير معًا في المجد
♪I once had you to see the whole world together♪
♪ لقد جعلتك ذات مرة ترى العالم كله معًا
(Do not sell alcohol to minors. Underage drinking is not permitted.)
(لا تبيع الكحول للقصر. لا يُسمح بتناول المشروبات الكحولية دون السن القانونية).